export const Reasoningquestions  = {
    topic: 'Reasoning',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
 
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'There are five rods K, L, M, N, and O. The weight of O is twice the weight of L. The weight of L is equal to the weight of K and M taken together. The weight of M is twice the weight of K. The weight of N is thrice the weight of M. If the weight of N is 90 kg. What will be the weight of O?',
      choices: ['105 kg', '60 kg', '120 kg', '90 kg'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '90 kg',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is the wrong term in the following series? CMQ, FPT, JTX, OYC, UFI',
      choices: ['FPT', 'OYC', ' JTX', 'UFI'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'UFI',
    },
    {
      question:
        'In a certain code,A % B means - A is the brother of B, A & B means - A is the mother of B, A @ B means - A is the daughter of B, A $ B means - A is the father of B and A # B means - A is the sister of B. If K $ Z % U & H # N @ T, how is T related to U?',
      choices: ['Sister', 'Husband', 'Wife', 'Brother'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Husband',
    },
    {
      question: 'Five persons A,B,C,D and E are comparing the number of books which they have bought recently. A bought more number of books than C and E, but not the highest. B bought more number of books than exactly one person. Then which of the following bought the highest number of books?',
      choices: ['C', 'D', 'B', 'E'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'D',
    },
    {
      question: '95% of the students in a class have taken Marketing, 80% have chosen Finance, 84% have chosen Operations (ops), and 90% have chosen Human Resources (HR). What is the maximum and minimum percentage of people who have chosen all of the four?',
      choices: ['80% and 56%', '95% and 53%', ' 80% and 49%', '80% and 51%'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '80% and 49%',
    },
    {
      question: ' Five teachers P, Q, R, S and T teach a group of students in sequence between 9 and 2 pm. Each teacher teaches for one hour. Q takes the first class. S teaches just after T, R teaches before P and T. Who takes the second class from 10 am to 11 am?',
      choices: ['S', 'R', 'P', 'T'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'R',
    },
    {
      question: ' Arrange the words in the following list in a meaningful order. 1. Money 2. Social standing 3. Education 4. Wellbeing 5. Work',
      choices: ['1,5,3,2,4', '2,1,3,5,4', '3,5,1,2,4', '5,4,2,1,3'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '3,5,1,2,4',
    },
    {
      question: "How am I related to my grandmother's only child's husband's mother?",
      choices: ['Grandmother', 'Mother', 'Sister', 'Aunt'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Grandmother',
    },
    {
      question: "John loses his way in a very dense jungle. He travels away from his tent at random but mathematical in a very interesting sense. He walks one mile east first, then half a mile north. Then 1/4 mile to the west, 1/8 mile to the south, and so on to complete the loop. Finally, how far away from his camp is he, and in which direction is he heading?",
      choices: ['0.98 miles', '0.56 miles', '0.76 miles', '0.44 miles'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '0.76 miles',
    },
    {
      question: "A young lady departs from her home. She walks 30 meters in a north-westerly direction, then 30 meters in a south-westerly direction. She then travels 30 meters to the southeast. She finally makes her way back to her residence. In which direction does she seem to be heading?",
      choices: ['Northeast', 'Southeast', 'Southwest ', 'Northwest'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Northeast',
    },
  ],
}

